##### Free Shipping On All Antennas - Use Promo: **FREESHIP**

    * [Top 5 Reasons To Get  
        An Antenna](https://www.rcaantennas.net/top-reasons/ "Top 5 Reasons To Get<br>An Antenna")

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: Sep 28, 2020

VOXX International Corporation and its subsidiaries, affiliates and brands that link to this policy (all collectively referred to as "VOXX International", "we", "us" or "our" in this Privacy Policy) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. This Privacy Policy will inform you as to how we look after, use, and share your personal data when you visit our websites, download and use our mobile applications, and interact with us offline, and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND HOW WE HANDLE YOUR INFORMATION. BY USING ANY OF OUR WEBSITES OR APPLICATIONS, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT WE WILL COLLECT, USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION AS SET FORTH BELOW. IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, ADDITIONAL INFORMATION APPLICABLE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS IS BELOW IN THE SECTION TITLED "TERMS APPLICABLE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ONLY."

#### 1\. CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We (or our service providers on our behalf) may collect the following categories of information:

**Identifiers** such as:

* First name, last name, and title
* Contact data including postal address (billing and shipping), email address and telephone number
* Internet protocol address ("IP Address"), unique personal identifiers, login names, usernames, social media, instant messaging or other online identifiers

**Commercial Information** including:

* Payment card details such as credit and debit card numbers, name on the credit card utilized, expiration date, cvv number, associated addresses, credit card provider, and signature
* Transaction data such as order number, serial number, metrics regarding your purchases from us, order confirmation with payment confirmation, and delivery information
* Information about your customer service interactions with us such as the content of your conversations with us (including recordings of phone calls and transcripts of live chats), the help topic that you select, any details that you provide about the circumstances of your request when requesting a repair, return, warranty service, or other customer service, and the date and time of our communications with you regarding such requests

**Usage Data** such as information about how you use our websites, including data we acquire from cookies on the websites (see [Cookie Policy](https://www.rcaantennas.net/cookie-policy/)) as well as performance data regarding the email marketing communications that we send to you

**Location Data** based on your IP address, zip code and time zone

**Account or Profile Data** including your username and password, purchase or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses, location data including city/state/zip/country, birth date and month for promotional purposes, and activity levels

**Internet Activity and Device Information**, such as primary and mobile browser type and version, primary and mobile email client and operating system, and browsing behavior

**Employment Information** such as professional or employment-related information contained in your resume or other documents you may submit to apply for positions with us

#### 2\. SOURCES OF DATA

We collect data from the following sources:

**Direct Interactions With You**. You may provide information such as Identifiers, Commercial Information, and Account or Profile Data when you:

* Visit our websites or use our applications
* Purchase our products or services
* Create an account or profile on our websites
* Contact us via email, phone, mail or live chat
* Seek customer service
* Subscribe to receive news from us
* Request marketing to be sent to you
* Enter a competition, promotion or survey
* Give us feedback

**Automatically**. As you interact with our websites and applications, we may automatically collect data such as Internet Activity and Device Information, Usage Data using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies, such as those displaying our videos, social media posts, and marketing messages. Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.rcaantennas.net/cookie-policy/) for further details. We may combine data automatically collected from you with other personal information about you.

**Third parties or publicly available sources**. We may receive personal data about you from third parties and public sources such as:

* Order & Payment. When you make a purchase online, you will be re-directed to our commerce platform vendor. We do not receive your full credit card, debit card or other financial information when you make a payment- such information is provided directly to the vendor. However, we do receive information about your purchase and your contact information (e.g. name, credit card type, last four digits of your credit or debit card number, email address, mailing address, phone number). We will keep a record of your purchases. We may collect tax identification numbers you submit for tax-exempt purposes.
* Social Media. We are active on social media, including Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, and LinkedIn ("Social Media"). Anything you post on Social Media is public information and will not be treated confidentially. We may post (or re-post) on our websites and Social Media pages any comments or content that you post on our Social Media pages. Your use of Social Media is governed by the privacy policies and terms of the providers that own and operate those websites and not by this Policy. We encourage you to review those policies and terms.

**Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies**. We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and other tracking technologies (collectively "Cookies") on our websites. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of our websites may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.rcaantennas.net/cookie-policy/).

**Analytics**. We use analytics providers including Google® Analytics to collect and process information about your use of our websites. These analytics providers set cookies on your browser or device, and then your web browser will automatically send information to them. They use this information to provide us with reports that we use to better understand and measure how users interact with our websites.

We may also implement additional add-on services to Google® Analytics, such as:

* **Demographics and Interest Reporting**, which gathers information such as the age and gender of users, along with certain interests those users express through their purchasing activities and other online activities, by tracking users across websites and across time.
* **Remarketing with Google® Analytics**, which uses user behaviors on our Site and within our App to help us identify users for our remarketing campaigns.
* **Google® Display Network Impression Reporting**, which provides us information about how often our ads are shown.

To learn more about how Google® uses data, visit [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy) and Google's page on "[How Google® uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)." You may download the [Google® Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) for each web browser you use, but this does not prevent the use of other analytics tools. To learn more about Google® Analytics cookies, visit [Google® Analytics Cookie Usage on Websites](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage).

**Interest-based Advertising**. We use third parties and/or service providers for interest-based or targeted advertising services. These services may serve advertisements on our behalf that are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to websites (including our websites) over time and across different websites. The data collected may be associated with your personal information. These advertisements may appear on our websites and on other websites, and may be sent to you via email.

We use Google® Ads to serve ads across various websites. Google® uses Cookies to collect data about your visits to our websites to generate targeted advertisements to you on other websites that you visit. To opt-out of this type of advertising by Google, to customize your ad preferences, or to limit Google's collection or use of such data, visit [Google's Safety Center](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools) and [Google's Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) and follow [Google's personalized ad opt-out instructions](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en&ref_topic=7048998). Opting out will not affect your use of the websites.

To change your preferences with respect to certain online ads or to obtain more information about ad networks and online behavioral advertising, visit [National Advertising Initiative Consumer opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Program](https://www.aboutads.info/). Changing your settings with individual browsers or ad networks will not necessarily carry over to other browsers or ad networks. As a result, depending on the opt-outs you request, you may still see our ads. Opting-out of targeted advertising does not opt you out of all ads, just those targeted to you.

**Video Content**. Our websites contain videos and embedded content provided by VOXX International and other parties, including visible content and/or feeds scripts embedded in the websites' code. VOXX International and such other parties may collect data about how you interact with such content. For example, YouTube may collect usage data on videos embedded on the websites. Even if you do not watch videos, YouTube may still collect certain information about your interactions with our websites if you are signed into your YouTube account or Google® account when accessing our websites. YouTube, LLC is owned by Google®. Please see Google's [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US) for more information.

**Maps**. The websites contain maps provided by third parties and/or service providers to help you locate nearby dealers. We and such other parties may collect data about how you interact with the maps. For example, Google® may collect usage data on maps embedded on the websites. Even if you do not interact with the maps, Google®may still collect certain information about your interactions with our websites if you are signed into your Google® account when accessing our websites. Please see Google's [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US) for more information.

#### 3\. PURPOSES FOR COLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We have set forth below the categories of data we may collect from you described in Section 1 above and the purpose for the collection and use of the data.

| Category of Information | Purpose/Activity |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | To register your Account or Profile as a customer or dealer<br><br>To process and deliver your order or to facilitate warranty or customer service<br><br>To manage our relationship with you<br><br>To provide marketing communications<br><br>To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you, including email marketing, and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you<br><br>To protect our legal rights and rights of third parties |
| Commercial Information | To process and deliver your order or to facilitate warranty or customer service<br><br>To manage our relationship with you<br><br>To provide marketing communications<br><br>To improve products<br><br>To protect our legal rights and rights of third parties |
| Internet Activity and Device Information<br><br>Usage Information<br><br>Location Data | To help with proper website and app function<br><br>To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you, including email marketing, and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you<br><br>To use data analytics to improve our website, applications, products/services |
| Marketing and Communications Data<br><br>Account and Profile Data | To manage our relationship with you<br><br>To provide marketing communications<br><br>To enable you to complete a survey<br><br>To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you, including email marketing, and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you<br><br>To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you |
| Employment Information | To evaluate your candidacy for the position you apply for |

#### 4\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We may share your personal data with the categories of parties set out below:

**Subsidiaries and Affiliates**. We may share personal information with our employees, VOXX International subsidiaries and affiliates who have a need to know the information for our business purposes.

**Third-Parties and/or Service Providers**. We may share personal information with third parties and/or service providers that provide services for us. For example, we may share personal information with vendors to help us host and manage the websites; provide targeted advertising and other marketing; improve the content and functionality of the websites; perform data analysis and statistical analysis; troubleshoot problems with the websites; provide payment processing services and online storefronts; provide public relations; provide learning management systems; provide email services; provide data processing; provide warranty and other customer and product service; and support or provide the security of the websites.

**Manufacturers and Brand Owners**. We may share personal information with third party product manufacturers, or brand owners or licensors (for those third party brands that we distribute), for the purpose of informing such entities of details with respect to any claimed product performance, safety, compliance, or other issue.

**Government Officials/Law Enforcement**. We will cooperate with law enforcement and other governmental agencies, and may disclose personal information: (a) if we believe in good faith we are legally required to disclose that personal information, (b) if we are advised to disclose personal information by our legal counsel, or (c) when necessary to identify, contact or bring a legal action against someone who may cause or be causing harm to, or interfering with our legal rights or those of any other party.

**Professional Advisors**. We may share personal information with our professional advisors, such as our attorneys, accountants, financial advisors and business advisors, in their capacity as advisors to us.

**Change in Ownership**. In the event (a) we are subject to a change of control, (b) the websites change ownership, in whole or in part, or (c) of a bankruptcy, receivership or a similar transaction, we may provide personal information to the subsequent owner(s).

**Other**. We may share personal information with third parties and/or service providers when explicitly requested by or consented to by you, or for the purposes for which you disclosed the personal information to us as indicated at the time and point of the disclosure (or as was obvious at the time and point of disclosure).

#### 5\. THIRD-PARTY LINKS

The VOXX International websites may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications not owned by us. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections will allow those third parties to collect and/or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements or practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites or to any data that you provide to third parties. When you leave our websites, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

#### 6\. CHILDREN

The VOXX International websites are not directed at children. We do not knowingly collect, use, or share personal information from children under 13. If a parent or legal guardian learns that their child provided us with personal information without his or her consent, please contact us and we will make commercially reasonable attempts to delete such personal information.

#### 7\. DATA SECURITY

We maintain appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. These employees, agents, contractors, and other third parties will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We maintain procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

You understand that no data transmission over the internet or a mobile device can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we do not guarantee the security of Personal Information and you provide Personal Information at your own risk.

#### 8\. DATA RETENTION

We will retain your personal data in accordance with applicable law.

#### 9\. TERMS APPLICABLE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ONLY

This Section provides additional terms that apply to residents of California. In the event of a conflict between this Section and the remainder of this Policy, this Section shall take precedence for California residents. In this Section only, any capitalized terms not defined in this Policy have the meanings set forth in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the "CCPA").

Categories of Personal Information Collected. In the last 12 months, we collected the following categories of Personal Information set forth in Section 1 above:

* Identifiers
* Commercial Information
* Usage Data
* Account and Profile Data
* Location Data
* Internet and Device Activity
* Employment Information

**Categories of Sources from which the personal information was collected**. Set forth above in Section 2 above.

**Business or commercial purpose for collecting personal information**. Set forth above in Section 3 above.

**Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose**. In the last 12 months we disclosed the following categories of Personal Information set forth in Section 1 above for our Business Purposes:

* Identifiers
* Commercial Information
* Usage Data
* Account and Profile Data
* Location Data
* Internet and Device Activity

**Your Right to Opt-out of the Sale of Your Information**. You have the right to opt out of the Sale of your personal information as defined by California law.

In the last 12 months we have not Sold, and we currently do not Sell, your Personal Information.

**Your Rights to Access and Deletion**. California residents have certain rights under the CCPA, such as the right to request certain information or request deletion of their personal information. Subject to certain limitations such as (a) exceptions permitted by applicable law and (b) verification of your identity, California residents may exercise the following rights with regard to their Personal Information:

Right to Access. You have the right to access any of the following which occurred in the prior 12-month period: (a) the categories of Personal Information we collected from you, (b) the categories of sources from which the Personal Information was collected, (c) the business or commercial purpose for collecting your Personal Information, (d) the categories of third parties with whom we shared your Personal Information, (e) the specific pieces of Personal Information we collected from you (i.e. "data portability"), and (f) a list of categories of Personal Information we disclosed for a Business Purpose in the last 12 months.

Right to Deletion. You have a right to request that we delete Personal Information we collected from you. We will comply with such request, and direct our service providers to do the same, subject to certain exceptions permitted by applicable law.

How to Exercise Your Rights of Access and Deletion. To exercise your California rights described in this Section, you may submit your request to us by contacting us at either of the following:

Email: [privacy@voxxintl.com](mailto:privacy@voxxintl.com)

Verifying Your Request. In order to verify your request, you must provide sufficient information to allow us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected Personal Information, and you must describe your request with sufficient detail to allow us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to your request.

When we receive your request to exercise your rights under the CCPA: (a) we will acknowledge receipt of your request; (b) we will try to match the information you provide in making the request with information we already maintain about you; (c) if required to verify your identity, we may ask you to provide additional information, including personal information; (d) we will consider various factors when determining how to verify your identity, such as the sensitivity and value of the data, the risk of harm, the likelihood of fraud, etc.

We will only use personal information we collect during the verification process for the purpose of verifying your identity. If you maintain an account with us, we may use that account to respond to your request and/or verify your identity. If we are unable to verify your identity as required by applicable laws and regulations, we will decline to comply with your request, and let you know why.

When We Will Respond. We will try to respond to your request for access or deletion within 45 days. If we require additional time, we will inform you of the reason and extension period. Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your Personal Information to you. We may charge a fee to process or respond to your request if it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.

Authorized Agent. You have a right to submit requests to exercise your rights under the CCPA through an authorized agent. If you choose to use an authorized agent, you must (a) provide signed permission to that authorized agent to submit requests on your behalf, (b) verify your identity directly with us, and (c) directly confirm that you granted permission to the authorized agent to submit the request on your behalf. For clarity, you are required to verify the identity of both yourself and the authorized agent.

We may deny a request from an authorized agent if we do not have proof that they are authorized by you to act on your behalf.

**Non-Discrimination**. You have a right to exercise the above requests and we will not discriminate against you for exercising these rights.

**California Shine the Light**. Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, if you are a California resident, you have the right to obtain: (a) a list of all third parties to whom we may have disclosed your Personal Information within the past year for direct marketing purposes, and (b) a description of the categories of Personal Information disclosed, by contacting us via our Data Privacy Manager as set forth above.

**Do Not Track**. We do not respond to Do Not Track requests.

#### 10\. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR DUTY TO INFORM US OF CHANGES

This version was last updated on Sep 28, 2020.

**We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the websites**.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

#### 11\. CONTACT DETAILS

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the data privacy manager using the details set out below.

Full name of legal entity: VOXX International Corporation

Email address: [privacy@voxxintl.com](mailto:privacy@voxxintl.com)

Postal address: 180 Marcus Blvd, Hauppauge, NY 11788

* Warning — Fraudulent Job Postings [Click Here](https://www.rcaantennas.net/careers/warning/ "Careers Warning")

#### FOR UPDATES

#### FOLLOW US

© 2024 VOXX Accessories Corp.

product specifications are subject to change without notification.

We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. [Learn More](https://www.rcaantennas.net/cookie/ "Cookie Policy") [I Accept](javascript:setCA())
